

AKMAL HARITH

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Objective

Analytical-minded creative team player with a background in strong designing, planning, and maintenance of software programs, desirous of the role of Software Engineer to hone technical skills and expertise along designing creative software and products as per the clients' needs and enhance the reputation of your organisation.

Personal Details

Address

6607, Jalan Melati 9 , Taman Indahpura , 81000, Kulai, Johor

Email

akmalharith58@gmail.com

Mobile No. 018-463 2550

Skills

Communication Language

Malay English



Programming Language

C++ Java

Html



References

Dr Noraswaliza Binti Abdullah Academic Advisor

T: +6062702468

E: noraswaliza@utem.edu.my FTMK,UTeM

Dr Mohd Sanusi Bin Azmi Dean FTMK , UTeM

T: +6062702472 E: sanusi@utem.edu.my FTMK,UTeM

Education

Diploma in Information Technologies Universiti Teknikal Malaysia Melaka Melaka 2021 - 2024

Obtained CGPA of 3.73 Receive Dean's Award in Semester 1 and 2

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia Sekolah Menengah Sains Muar (SAMURA) Johor 2016 - 2021

Obtained 2A+s , 5As and 1A- in Mathematics,History,Malay Langange,English Languange,Physics,Islamic Education,Technical Communication Graphics and Additional Mathematics

Experience

HID GLOBAL Sdn. Bhd.

Kulai,Johor

April 2021 - Jun 2021

Production Worker

Monitored Machinery in Operation to identify concerns and make corrections or report complex problems

Supported current production needs by moving items between equipment, conveyors and staging areas

Nasi Kandaq Royale Daun Pisang

Kulai, Johor

July 2022 - September 2022

Bartender

Manage to handle orders on peak hour with systematic Can make an order less than a minute

Extracurricular Activities

Universiti Teknikal Malaysia Melaka, Melaka

A member of UTeM's Orchestra Team as Logiistics Assistant, tubist and bassist. Have perfored in many shows in UTeM such as UTeM 18th Convocation Day

Sekolah Menengah Sains Muar (SAMURA), Johor

President of Arts and Culture Club , bassist of Samura Band and member of Gamelan Gemalai Sari Team. Have performed many shows and won Gamelan Competition (2019)